We're going to go for a Monday, August 19th, and we'll be 24, but the patient, if you'd
imagine, would want to hurt us to hurt you.
My father, I've got a very slippery floor that we can kind of gather freely and talk
about how I did it.
I'm creating work for your spirit wisdom.
It's a subtle podcast.
I thank you for your peace that passes all in a state.
We ask now if you're guided in some of these and we will be able to let you down and all
of our public service.
Thank you, God, for our first responders and all of our lives.
I'm going to allow the public service to inform you recently.
So, Father, watch over us.
Keep us under your hand protection.
We create the same suggested Jesus Christ's presence and pull it in.
Amen.
I'd like to thank you to the students who have been to the United States of America.
We can see the great public, we're always in stands.
We're amazed.
We can be able to look at their energy and best to grow.
We're going to make good number four, which is the help of giving us good
to personal parents.
This is not going to change it up a little bit.
We're going to go ahead and go to the second session.
Right after a public speaking, that will, you guys can be trained for quickly going to play.
That will go to the third thing else.
All right?
Okay.
So, first up, we have the safety pears.
Please come to the mic and say, can I have these?
Do you think my name is Stacey Pierce?
And my name is Grand Eggwood.
I'm a very Asian-seal aging.
And I just wanted to...
Just about a few things that I've heard,
who the seniors talked about last week.
And just wanted to come to point out that Grand Eggwood is here
to assist the seniors center.
We have the senior friends.
We offer that to all our seniors in our service and opportunity
to apply for up to $10,000.
And then we can get that $2,000 operational on those automatically.
I pulled back, and you guys have a copy of this.
Because of that, today.
I went back today and pulled back as far as 20 or 15.
The mind is the same center.
It has asked for that program.
And we're in every year.
Up until this year.
This is the first year that we're on asked for the program.
This is the first year that they honestly did not apply
for the operational program.
Which is an automatic.
And whenever I pulled and I spoke to Gaye,
she really didn't have any interest.
It was pretty much the then deal she developed that the audience were going to take in the center.
I explained that her that would be better if she would go ahead and just at least apply for something.
That way, for whatever reason, if the city did not take the center, and the purist did take it,
because at least we could move those funds to an other center.
But at least it felt to the city, she would have that right.
And it was all for our board, now it's virtually too late.
We did give them the $2,000, but $10,000 is almost out of the picture, because she chose not to do it.
And you have your packet every year that they applied, every year except for one, they did not receive any part of the $10,000.
I can't tell you why that reason.
I was not, and I'm a director at that point.
I'm assuming it's probably lack of funding, low funding that year.
There were probably more things to more priority as far as those in refrigerators and things like that.
But this is something that they did not apply for this year.
Because they called it for an event deal.
There were something else, and it brought to my attention.
This is the first time I've heard that it's going to come to the director as a 2018.
And there was a senior intervention.
They couldn't cook.
They couldn't use our kitchen.
That's never been an issue.
That has never been brought to my attention until last midnight.
Those student holders.
They threw a fly in time including this year.
And after we're so over refrigerator from microwave and dishwasher,
there's plenty of room in that center.
We could have helped them to build a bad day-type kitchen.
We better than say that it's the portal.
You get three minutes.
Please, please, be careful not to crowd or do it.
And we can't out of song.
So that can be juiced out of it.
My name is Judy Saude late.
I'm a man here.
I'm the president of Doc Services Board.
Docs is in the current facility now for 32 years.
As Stacey said, until we talked about brands and everything.
There was an issue last midnight that, you know,
if they only had to give us like 30 days to know that sort of 60 days to know something like that.
We don't give it any notice.
BJ called Doc Marm and talked to her.
And because you live on it for being bring it,
but it was going to be given to us all access to going to be transferred to the rate drive.
They can also say that they were hoping they would get it done
for the heck that it fires.
So it could be a done deal.
What I want to understand is why
in the bylaws, it says all SS and we're back to the city, and I know there are some
regulations there are things that it seems to me that we were in a partnership with
the senior citizens there because we've been there for 32 years and very meals. But we
were not contacted, we were not asking anything, we were not, it was not discussed with us,
and I know that our director has several times gone to the senior citizens board, and
suggested, you know, let us look at it, we manage the doctorate's as many as the senior
citizen and the brother, with the help of the city of brother. And we've made sense for us to
be able to do that, that that was a simple thing to consider. They're all the way to this,
it was mentioned several times. We just felt like that the city, since the access, when we
brought back to the city, if they resolved, they would make a sense of the city to handle it
and accept proposals. Now, we're from a tribe, from dog services or maybe any other entity that
would like to come in and try to manage and see their citizens in the city. And that's, that is there
been an option for us. And if we start to like, we do like that as the best price for us
because that way the one on the any interaction in the old service to be the people where the
need is people that, and I give you all, which I think you all have copied. We have some testimonials
from some senior citizens, you know, the services that we provide, plus the one on one, the human
contact that they get, or someone every single day, they would not have otherwise. And we just want
you to consider that. Thank you.
Thank you.
That's the winning problem?
I just want to say this program is a thoughts in most of us, my age. And my husband is blind, I do not
know why both of us are here. So we do welcome, thank you all, which one of us thought.
We don't see you.
Thank you.
Stella, heavy?
He was Stella, heavy.
And I go to the United States at nine drive to meet the village.
for this year's citizens, and they had done the other part that good because when my husband passed away,
I was really breathing over the end, and I got to go down there and I got to be visit with other people,
and I really came out with my shyness, and my backgrounds, and I really appreciate seeing your citizens committed, thank you very much with you.
Early in life.
Can you answer me in terms of what's going on?
Okay.
I can't agree with you, right?
That's all that's going to be going on.
Thank you, Joe.
We'll see what's here.
We have thoughts and same services.
Number one, two thousand and nineteen.
I'll stand up.
What need?
In the war plan for it.
And it seems to be right.
Since I've been going to the off-service of the...
We've renewed friendship with people I had to see, and along, we've got to get a place to go every day,
subject to people and breaks up loneliness to get close.
I'm not feeling that the Senate is not there.
A lot of people are among them.
A lot of them are among them.
And not only one of this.
They're very helpful.
They're learning everything.
So I think they're trying to slide them.
Sit down.
Something that deserves to be a great asset.
Thank you.
One of the most.
I'd like to read all of this in consideration
about not to be able to program.
Because as we get older, a lot of times,
it just keeps us, you know, and every time.
So I think that they have to deal with that.
Mr. Harrow.
You're somewhere somewhere.
And you're speaking back to the box.
And I didn't know that I could give my meal.
I'm six years old now.
I give my meal.
I'm looking for a meal.
And we don't want to do that.
It's great time.
We have family eat.
We eat.
That was my strategy.
It's like that.
Anyone else wants to eat.
If you want to eat, you can eat.
If you want to do that.
Yes.
Okay.
But there's just one thing I want you to make.
There's so much confusion without people.
I have to pay the sleepers in.
Well, one stops.
It was in the slide.
Let's go to the meeting.
I want to start by that comment.
I'm going to be changing the dirtier box.
And what I really was talking about is if the site barn
older merkins act and the poverty and nutrition sites.
I just said that's clear that there would be no cost
in your sick general.
What I want you to say is that it is very important to us.
And it would be best if we are able to continue utilizing our space
at the senior center.
I know you guys have seen what it looks like.
It's your space.
You see how large the space is that we live.
We are willing to compromise on it.
And have to do a solution.
However, it's best if we don't have to disrupt service.
And we would like to continue.
Anyone else?
We're going to take a picture.
Because I'm going to put a former vice president there at the senior center.
I was there for a several years prior to a COVID and even a little bit during the COVID.
The reason I'm here today is because I'm thinking of going to have some of the seniors,
especially the activist senior center.
That is a likely good.
That's a very good.
Socialized and anywhere else together.
Some of us are going to go to the gym, some of them can.
I'd like to see that still be the same.
Now I have the idea of what the plan is or what the seniors actually is.
But I hope they have a thanks to the government.
Because the arts centers are still our vice people.
They need to be easy.
They're going to pay our not being wise.
And we need that.
We need that wisdom.
I need to say it for the ways.
It's what's going to happen.
They don't have a place to go.
They're just going to say it all.
They're just going to buy out.
I think they're going to have a special.
Now you see each other.
I'm going to touch them there.
And I hope them to stay active.
I was there for a while.
I'm the only way my family that got it.
I hope they're back to you.
And the result of shock.
Because I was adamant about if I was to carry it and I didn't know I had it.
I did it to learn my seniors.
I would've felt bad to learn what to catch the way.
I still feel that way.
I have friends out there.
I don't want to see them, not go without anything today.
I'm not going to continue to have a place where they can exercise, they can self-verbalize,
they can play games, just like the younger ones of us.
When I was a vice president, I was too young, and now, I'm too years into it, I'm a member, as well.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you, Rick.
The question of me, I mean, my name is John Parker, and I'm not a member of the senior citizens,
but I have a question, is the officers?
Are they going to quit serving the city and my name?
Just because of what's going on in the senior service, then that's not question.
Did anybody answer that?
Did they go into this?
Did you start?
Did anybody have an answer for that?
I'm sorry.
We're all attracted.
We're all attracted to the council.
But we will.
I'm sure that will come out before we go.
Okay.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
We need to do this in the council.
All of those citizens in the community that are present.
My name is Craig Hart, Robert G. for the Purity Tribe.
We couldn't be more excited about what a possible partnership.
It could look like what that is.
Our goal is to make it a high-ranked active activities for all the senior member community.
Just like we've done with our work in the community.
And so we're very excited about that.
We believe that dogs are not just for any other side or dogs.
But the kids in here in the community.
And if that happened, what's your main necessity?
Permission.
Thank you.
I mean, we take a session.
We take a session.
We're about 25 and 46.
Specifically, we'll be back in the next session.
We'll later about another minute and a minute.
This is taking a session with that obviously five and 26.
And we'll infer the 10 waves for the results of the whole schedule.
Thank you, man.
I'll get you a place that people can't hear me.
Can you help hear me?
Can you help me?
I'll help you.
This is not very good.
I'll feel like I'm yelling.
I can't hear me.
Okay.
So, my pleasure being with everyone in the night.
I appreciate your opportunity to have a conversation about this in four issues.
We can't hear you.
I want to start out with saying that I can't help.
I compliment the mind and senior center of the evening.
You're going to have a grafted, it's original.
Documents.
The other thing that can be, in a way, it's in compliance with the whole.
It's very clear to my review that the Indian tends to comply with the General Corporation Act of the State of Oklahoma,
as well as the portion of the statute that applies to not for proper entities like this entity.
So, you can never guard a very pleased that that was in the steps of replacing the original.
So, one of the things that you want to be usually taught in the review of the articles.
One of them is Article 8 of the article.
Article 8 deals with the disillusion of the Indian.
Now, I'm not being here for the part of the Indian.
I'm understanding that there are proposals that amount to a practical disillusion of this entity.
Transferences and disillusion of the organization,
disillusion of all of the main assets of the organization are to go to the city land.
I think I've heard some comments tonight.
We might quickly get one of our chance.
So, that's the way this entity was disillusioned.
Under the sanctions of the State in particular.
of the General Corporation Act, which I mentioned a lot ago, one of the things that becomes clear
is that corporations are established to be in business or in operation. One of the things
under 18 section of the 10, 16 is this provision. It says that corporations can make donations
for the public welfare, for example. In that regard, it's consistent in my experience, the assets
of the city are used for the welfare of the citizens of the city. So that regard, I think,
that again, this fits with one of the organizations that I can photograph. So that's
a significant line for the law. Also, in terms of the intersection of the statute, I don't
even think in section 588, this provision makes it clear that not for the public entities
can hold and dispose of their assets and sit with the purposes of the corporation. So
that regard, because it's clear that one of the purposes of the corporation was the benefit
of the city management and the amount of dissolution. It would be insistent with the enemy purpose
for the assets of the transfer of the city. So, basically, I'm not going to do the general documents
of the organization, I understand the fact, I'm certainly recommending that the city request that
the enemy is to be dissolved, but the asset that you can answer to the city. That is the
way to stable the drives the houses. I will mention that one of the things that must happen is a Bible
on C3 and the Inexit, a tax term for enough of the property in the federal tax area. Whenever a Bible
seems to be dissolved, it has to go through the process. One of the questions is that tax, during
that this provision of the process, the IRS of the Exit Handsome, is, did you dispose of the assets
of this enemy consistent with your governing documents in the system center, senior citizens center,
breaks over the assets to the city, that's consistent with the governing documents. Anything else
will not be insistent with the governing documents and will likely further tax liability back now.
The next slide of the ability to follow on the board of directors of the end, may I?
So, it's all not a 25.
The question is, is there a motion, the way it drives to the assets from the city,
to the businesses that are there, and all the products, the transfer assets, to the pure tribe,
the minions of the public.
Seeing the motion, the result of the city of Iowa,
the city of Missouri, and the council, are authorized with necessary to seek a determination
by the public board of District Court,
to come and get all the characteristics of the court,
or the right to the city of Iowa, and the big ownership of the assets
and what I'm seeing as there, the corporate, and all the solutions of that entity.
I'll get a motion.
I'll do a five.
Can I let you go?
OK.
Thank you, Mr. President.
Mr. President, can you take a second under the investigation?
Or back from the agenda?
New, you have the opportunity to,
the genders, that action was actually in the city council agenda.
So, technically, I think we're back to the agenda of the number 5 of the,
If we're going back to our great service, let's play it now.
Yeah, pop, okay, pop, pop.
Okay, pop, pop.
Okay, pop.
Pop.
I would like to ask that then, from the power of public or gerving it,
I would like to say about 2,030 dollars.
All right.
I would like to demonstrate what we're receiving.
This is for professional services and discussion.
If you're entering the G203,
there's between the four two July 15th, 2020-4,
on the opposite of the line.
So we did such things.
This can take any issue.
We'd like to do a second plan.
We'd just question about the optimum method.
We'll be very careful with the field.
What we have to do now is in the transforcement setting.
So this will be, to discuss,...
...so we will play...
...so that we have to do 30,
if we don't want to discuss with you,
and then we have to evaluate the standards.
I'll come up with a room.
I'll speak to you.
East at extra levels.
So I'll call my phone to John Jackson.
John Jackson's partner.
That's what I'm talking about today.
Eight.
I'd drawn an operating board from American
to the Metro solution with treatment for re-haring software
involved in the office of our area,
if I'm lost, and if this is right.
Yes, this is an agreement for a software
that our young adults need to have to work properly.
Previous of the longer the game is supported.
So we have to have a great, and this is a great.
This is something we have to have more for our folks.
Yes, that's it.
How much does it work?
It's that.
So it's a total part of the process.
I think we're going to take care of it.
Now we're the manual, new manual.
I'm called Aswell Training Service, the SQL for ASCII team.
The deers play with L.C. for those two years old.
We're going to work on that.
We're directly going to buy staff.
We're going to bring the contract to take it on submission.
The fall required contract documents.
Gentlemen, trust me.
It's a city of my own and mine.
It's a special facility for you.
We have agreements with contracts in terms of the very beginning.
I said, hey, what are you supposed to do?
It's just a client service that's in terms of contracts.
Such as the case of the Hong Kong, Aswell Training Services.
I know this debaters was published in March 22, March 29,
in most of the city's website.
No good work of training.
I don't even want to be it.
I'm called Aswell Training Services.
We've been standing out for requesting quotes.
I ran away from the third.
Peter's painting was the only one that was there.
I know that there's a question of what it's.
If you have the sheet here, it talks about what it is.
It shows all the prices that they have here today.
This agreement includes a three, a three, a one-year extension.
If there's no charges.
And a staff recommends to a work and a specific.
We're going to take a quick pause for a second.
Anybody else believe you're one of the little nerds.
What a lovely, lovely.
Now we'll be in the state of Washington.
Yeah.
I'm going to go to the right.
Take a look.
This can't be so.
I'm going to take a quick break.
I'll take a quick break.
You're 29 and 87 miles a day.
But I'm going to go.
This is 4, Attected Check.
We'll see that's in the seminar before we can get.
By the name I'm probably my favorite one.
This is going to help this discussing with the state.
What I want to do with my five colleagues.
So we're actually using that data.
So there's kind of two things in here that they're doing.
First of all, this is, this will be made where I would like to mention that we here.
in like 10 points out this is their estimate so they have a really good
kind of game set.
What's your approach?
I think it's 10 points out now.
I'm going to talk to Mark, Mark.
Right.
Hello.
The extension of the National Service of Humanity.
They was right for Ray with the LLP.
The question here is really important about it.
Yes, this is just due to a date of our contract with the KWD
Answering in there.
This is under the purposes of the LLP.
We have a visa passing.
Turn by, suddenly.
The same question to prove.
The problem is that general is at the principal.
Well, an individual is the president's closest to the president
or phenomic or gene's workforce.
All right.
The question is being你说 the right word.
It means that the course of the big sessions, that we're on the 20th of a regular being launched again.
We'll call it over.